HiringCat AI QA - Integrations / Webhooks
Running: Integrations / Webhooks
Using saved authenticated browser session.
Opening integrations and creating/testing/deleting a real QA webhook.
UI Step 1: Fill webhook endpoint URL in visible integrations form.
UI STEP: Webhook endpoint form filled - url=https://example.com/hiringcat-ai-qa-ui-webhook-1785236612155
UI STEP: Create endpoint clicked and endpoint state refreshed - Visible webhook UI accepted the create action.
REQUEST: API POST /api/webhooks - {"url":"https://example.com/hiringcat-ai-qa-webhook-1785236612155","events":["application.submitted"]}
PASS: API response POST /api/webhooks - HTTP 201; {"id":"4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","url":"https://example.com/hiringcat-ai-qa-webhook-1785236612155","events":["application.submitted"],"isActive":true,"failureCount":0,"createdAt":"2026-07-28T11:03:41.4
REQUEST: API GET /api/webhooks -
PASS: API response GET /api/webhooks - HTTP 200; [{"id":"4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","url":"https://example.com/hiringcat-ai-qa-webhook-1785236612155","events":["application.submitted"],"isActive":true,"failureCount":0,"createdAt":"2026-07-28T11:03:41.
REQUEST: API PATCH /api/webhooks/4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f -
PASS: API response PATCH /api/webhooks/4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f - HTTP 200; {"id":"4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","url":"https://example.com/hiringcat-ai-qa-webhook-1785236612155","events":["application.submitted"],"isActive":false,"failureCount":0,"createdAt":"2026-07-28T11:03:41.
REQUEST: API POST /api/webhooks/4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f/test -
PASS: API response POST /api/webhooks/4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f/test - HTTP 200; {"event":{"id":"29c79bea-5525-4c8f-86e4-50407d78ac86","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","event":"application.submitted","payload":{"test":true,"message":"This is a test webhook from HiringCat.","webhookId":"4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f"},"
REQUEST: API DELETE /api/webhooks/4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f -
PASS: API response DELETE /api/webhooks/4c32d5c3-e98a-4ba7-8e8f-ac101943b92f - HTTP 200;
Result: PASS - Webhook integration was created, listed, toggled inactive, test-called, and deleted.